Zagoria, Sam National Labor Relations Board Photographs 6379 P
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Sam Zagoria National Labor Relations Board Photographs
1965- 1979
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Zagoria, Sam
6379 P
0.89 cubic feet
0.3 linear ft.
Photographs.
8450842
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, April 18, 2014
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, October 23, 2015
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 6379: Sam Zagoria National Labor Relations Board Papers
Zagoria, Samuel; National Labor Relations Board (NLRB); U.S. Conference of Mayors
8450842
- Photo Album contents - NLRB Photos: Attorney General Tom Clark, VP Richard Nixon, Strom Thurmond, George Meany, Frank McCulloch, and many more (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  8 photographs
- NLRB - White House (1965) -- Photo Album contents - (Box 1, Folder 2)
  14 photographs; Invitations; matchbooks; RSVP cards; Menus
- NLRB Photo (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Photographs from Career at U.S. Conference of Mayors Scrapbook -- 1970-1979 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  11 photographs
- Photographs from NLRB Career Scrapbook -- 1965-1968 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Photographs from NLRB Career Scrapbook -- 1968-1970 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Misc. NLRB photos - Ronald Reagan in one (Box 1, Folder 7)
  2 photographs
- Sam Zagoria -- 22 November 1965 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  1 photograph
- Photos [found in 6379, removed and placed here] (Box 1, Folder 9)
  Photos of Sam Zagoria with Clifford Case and Sylvia Zagoria
- Photographs from scrapbook "NLRB Career 1965-1966" (Box 1, Folder 10)
  see 6379, box 1, ff23
- Photographs from scrapbook - "CPSL appointment" (Box 1, Folder 11)
  see 6379, box 1, ff24
- Fulbright (Denmark) (Box 1, Folder 12)
  7 Photographs